

yeseulseo24@gmail.com | +82-10-9101-3120 yeseulseo.com | github.com/yeseulseo | linkedin.com/in/yeseulseo

Profile

A passionate UX Designer and an advocate of continuous communication to deliver intuitive digital products and interfaces. Have solid customer empathy build through experiences in student service, online marketing, and end-to-end UI, UX design and front-end development projects. Developed proficiency in the following skills:

- Heuristic Evaluation
- Information Architecture
- ◆ HTML & CSS

- Mobile-First Design
- Responsive Design
- User Research & Testing
- User Flows
- Visual Style Guide
- Wireframes & Prototypes

Experience

CareerFoundry, Remote (Berlin, Germany)

Certified UX Designer Course

September 2017 – September 2018

- Designed intuitive digital products, based on communication with users and solid design concepts
- Conducted 3 UI and UX design projects, and 1 front-end development project to bring the better user experiences:
 - **Portfolio Redesign:** Rebuilt a portfolio website using HTML, CSS and JavaScript considering the user experiences and adding proper interactions within the website
 - **FitJet:** A web application design project based on responsive design principles, providing exercise recommendations depending on users' preference and circumstances
 - **VELA:** A mobile application design project, providing weather forecast service for water sports enthusiasts, based on their geo-location
 - **Enjoy HSK:** A mobile application design project, targeting the users who study vocabularies for HSK examination

Seoul School of Integrated Sciences & Technologies, Seoul, South Korea

March 2017 - March 2018

Employee (Program Coordinator Equivalent)

- Managed a dual degree program which was held with Stony Brook University
- Built solid foundation of user analysis by supporting students' coursework and gathering their feedback
- Built rapport with the students (users) through open communication for students' satisfaction
- Improved the effectiveness of communication with the directors at Stony Brook University for the better program management
- Marketed the degree program via the official blog and the Facebook page

BeyondThis, Seoul, South Korea

April 2013 - August 2014

Online Marketing Associate

- Member of the startup company that developed a mobile mathematics-learning application
- Built background of user testing and research by analysing the application and marketing methods of similar products to attract more users
- Responsible for editing educational materials during the application development process
- Conducted marketing for the product via the official blog of BeyondThis

Education

CareerFoundry, Remote (Berlin, Germany)

September 2017 - September 2018

Certified UX Designer

- Trained intensively to attain proficiency in detailed UI and UX design trends and techniques
- Learned how to communicate with clients and colleagues, including directors, managers, data analysts and engineers, during design processes
- Learned visual design principles, including colour theory, iconography, grid system and layouts, to bring solid design concepts
- Learned principles of HTML, CSS and JavaScript for better communication with engineers

Sookmyung Women's University, South Korea

March 2012 - August 2017

B.A. in English Language and Literature

- Minor in Teaching (English)
- Participated in training program at the United Nations Office in Geneva, Switzerland (2013)

Northern Kentucky University, KY, USA

August 2014 - December 2014

Study Abroad Program

Studied at Northern Kentucky University as an exchange student in the autumn semester, 2014

UX Tools

- Adobe Illustrator
- Atom
- Balsamiq
- Figma

- GitHub
- InVision
- Marvel
- MS Office

- Optimal Workshop
- UsabilityHub
- Zeplin

UX Certificates

- Frontend Development for Designers (issued by CareerFoundry, September 2018)
- UX Certified Program (issued by CareerFoundry, July 2018)
- UI for UX Designers (issued by CareerFoundry, July 2018)
- UX Immersion (issued by CareerFoundry, May 2018)
- UX Fundamentals (issued by CareerFoundry, Oct 2017)

Languages

- Korean & English (native / fluent)
- Japanese (intermediate)
- Cantonese & French (basic)

Interests

- Gathering UI and UX design inspiration via social media
- Language learning
- Travel abroad